# **FAZA MURTADHO**

085347223920

faza.murtadho@gmail.com

Sleman, Yogyakarta

<u>LinkedIn</u> & <u>Portfolio Website</u>

#### **ABOUT**



Full Stack Developer with 1 year+ of experience creating responsive, user-friendly websites and applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Enthusiastic towards new tech in Front End Development for website. Looking to obtain and sharpen skills in the respective area.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



#### **Junior Full Stack Web Developer**

#### PT. Softem Mitra Indonesia, Jakarta

December 2022 - March 2024

- Probation period creating website using React JS with Tailwind CSS (Landing Page, Login Form, and Fetching API created by senior at work)
- Next 3 months Responsible for creating and maintaining Japanese Client Internal Programs for Transaction (Wholesale Products) using MVC Architecture Pattern with C# and ASP.NET.
- For the rest of time Responsible for creating, maintaining, bug fixing, and code review using Java with Springboot Framework and Thymeleaf for Front-End Development.

#### **Creating Forecasting Dashboard with Business Intelligence in Cryptocurrency for Decision Making**

#### Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

February 2022 - July 2022

 Obtain data sets via the website's Endpoint API, employ the ARIMA method for analysis, and culminate by crafting dashboards in Power BI connected to a MySQL database.

#### **Team Leader in Creating Field Monitoring and Administration Mobile Application**

#### PT. Kelola Jasa Artha, Surabaya

October 2021 - February 2022

- Led a cross-functional team in the successful development and launch of a field monitoring and administration mobile application, ensuring adherence to project timelines.
- Creating barcode scanner in mobile application to monitor field staff when distributing money using Android Studio with Java programming language.
- Created UI design for mobile applications using Figma and Android Studio.

# Team leader of Business Intelligence Team in the Development of a Web-Based Dashboard Management System for BUMDES NGINGAS during College Community Service

#### Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

July 2021 - December 2021

- Spearheaded a team of 5 members in the development of a user-friendly web-based dashboard management system for BUMDES NGINGAS to help streamline operations and improve decision-making processes.
- Created the management dashboard using Power BI and MySQL.

#### **Laboratory Assistant at Smart City and Cyber Security**

#### Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

July 2019 - July 2021

- Maintained laboratory equipment such as 40 computers, 3 switches, and 1 server.
- Maintained laboratory environment while providing support to lecturers regarding laboratory equipment.

#### **ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE**



# **Staff at Student Association of Information Technology**

# Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

# September 2019 - September 2020

- In charge of guiding new Information Technology students in acclimating to college life and the academic environment.
- Prepared Information Technology students to become members of the Information Technology Student Association.
- Social services

# **SKILLS**



- Front-End Website: Tailwind CSS, React
  JS, Thymeleaf.
- Visual Design: Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.
- Power BI.

Other Programming Language: JavaScript, Java, C#, HTML, Native Android (Java), Springboot, MVC Architecture.

# **EDUCATION**



# Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Computer Science (S. Kom)

GPA: 3.37